lineups.com 2019-06-03

# Privacy

By using the Service, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to amend this Privacy Policy and changes will come into effect immediately upon update to the Site. Your continued use of the Service constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy and any amendments. Our Terms of Service, see www.lineups.com/terms, take precedence over any conflicting provision of this Privacy Policy. Unless otherwise defined herein, capitalized terms shall have the meaning given to them in our Terms of Service. The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to enable you to understand how we collect, store, use and safeguard your personal information and for you to understand your rights in relation to that information.

As part of the Site account opening process and to allow us to provide services to you, we may ask you to provide us with certain personal information, including your name, postal address, telephone number, e-mail address and password as well as to certify that you are at least 18 years old or older in jurisdictions in which the minimum age for use of the Service is greater than 18. For the purposes of using the Service via the Mobile Software, you will be required to consent to the use of location-based services (LBS) by us to detect your geographic location. We may also use your information to verify your credentials from third parties including financial institutions, identification verification agencies and credit reference agencies for the purposes of us providing services to you. In addition, when you use the Service we store certain personal information, including information on your activity on the Site and information held on Devices (defined below) or systems that you use, to allow us to enhance the services that we provide to you. We, members of our Group, our affiliates and third parties providing services on our behalf will use your personal information for various purposes such as:

  * to confirm financial transactions,
  * to provide services to you;
  * identification and vetting purposes;
  * statistical analysis and research;
  * research and development;
  * marketing, market research and customer profiling;
  * data analysis;
  * to comply with licensing and regulatory requirements; and
  * to analyze your credit and fraud risk.

We may disclose your personal information:

  * if required to do so by law or by regulatory authority;
  * if we believe in good faith that such action is necessary:
  * to comply with any law or comply with legal process served on us;
  * to protect and defend our rights or property;
  * to any regulatory body or licensing body or authority;
  * to third parties for the purposes of settling or making payment in connection with any wager;
  * to any payment management or debt collection company engaged by us to handle payment and collection
  * processes to and from Users;
  * to third parties who provide services to us or on our behalf;
  * to any third party that purchases us or our business or any part of us or our business;

In addition to legally required disclosures as explained in this Privacy Policy, we may disclose your personal information to our employees, our agents and to third party service providers who use your personal information to provide services to us in respect of your being a User with Lineups.com Inc. We may combine your personal information collected from your use of the Service in accordance with this Privacy Policy with other information collected from you using other services operated by Lineups.com Inc. as well as all products which are related or ancillary thereto, including mobile and social networking services. We will treat this combined information in accordance with, and will use it for the purposes set out in this Policy. All recipients of your personal information shall be bound by applicable data protection laws to keep your personal information private at no less a level than that by which we are bound.

We may use your email address for the purpose of providing you with news, promotions and other marketing offers. We may also share your email address and phone number with our marketing partners for the purpose of providing you with marketing offers. Out of respect for your right to privacy we have provided you with an easy means by which you may stop receiving marketing offers via email. You may request at any time to no longer receive such offers by sending an email to info@lineups.com. If you request to discontinue receiving these offers we will remove your details from our marketing distribution lists and from any future lists we may share with our marketing partners. However, you may need to unsubscribe separately from marketing offers sent by partners who have received your contact details from us prior to your request to be removed from these lists.

Cookies are text-only strings of information that are downloaded to your personal desktop, laptop computer or mobile device (each a **“Device"** ) when you visit a website. They are then sent back to the originating website on each subsequent visit, or to another website that recognizes those cookies.

Cookies are very useful and are used for many different purposes. These include allowing you to navigate between pages efficiently, remembering your preferences, and generally improving user experience. Sometimes cookies are used to help ensure that adverts you see online are relevant to you and your interests. We use cookies in order to track referrals to our websites, to remember your preferences, to make our websites more responsive, and to generate anonymized statistical data, which we use to improve the user experience on our websites. We also use cookies to measure the effectiveness of our advertising campaigns, to limit the number of times you see an advertisement, to remember that you have visited a website, and to provide advertisements that are more relevant to your interests.

There are links to websites with whom we have a business relationship. We encourage you to read their Privacy Policies. We may also link to websites that are maintained by one or more of our business partners who are collecting your information pursuant to their own policies.

Lineups.com reserves the right to display any information you submit in your profile including, but not limited to, your screen name(s), real name and/or your winning results under the screen names of external websites you enter in your profile on Lineups.com
